<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Synapse Blog</title>
        <link>https://playsynapse.com/release</link>
        <description>Synapse Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 02:17:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[v0.0.3]]></title>
            <link>https://playsynapse.com/release/v0.0.3</link>
            <guid>https://playsynapse.com/release/v0.0.3</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 02:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[- Ability to reroll perks, for a price]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li>Ability to reroll perks, for a price</li></ul><h1>Changes</h1><ul><li>Death screen now shows level and perk summary at death</li><li>Player briefly flashes red and changes facial expression when taking damage</li><li>Corpses are displayed on unit death</li><li>Changed perk rarity color to background (was previously perk name)</li></ul><h1>Balance</h1><ul><li>Fixed issue where closest enemy to player was not being targeted</li><li>Fixed issue where selecting the attack range perk was breaking the SMG</li><li>Corrected calculation for adjusted armor perk</li><li>Improved critical damage calculation</li><li>Adjusted scaling of enemy health and damage</li><li></li></ul><h1>Bugfix</h1>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Release Notes</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[v0.0.4]]></title>
            <link>https://playsynapse.com/release/v0.0.4</link>
            <guid>https://playsynapse.com/release/v0.0.4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 01:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[- The game now has a name- Synapse!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li>The game now has a name- Synapse!</li><li>Created an instagram and registered playsynapse.com</li><li>Randomly spawn health and armor pickups on the level<ul><li>Pickups give cells if health pickup and player has max health</li><li>Armor pickup always adds armor</li><li>Pickups can spawn closer to player if less than 5 health</li></ul></li></ul><h1>Changes</h1><ul><li>Limited number of corpses on screen to 30</li><li>Made everything smaller on screen</li><li>Adjusted hitboxes to be a bit more forgiving for the player</li><li>Add a pickup spawn boost perk to reduce time between pickup spawns</li><li>Adjusted fire rate of weapons to make the game a bit more challenging</li><li>Significantly adjusted the number of enemies that spawn in later waves. You should be able to make it past level 15 now.</li><li>Updated the application icon and loading screen</li><li>Units become disinterested if far enough away from player</li><li>Units will flee if a threshold of units are killed in their proximity</li><li>15% chance to spawn enraged units with increased stats and no chance of threat</li><li>50% chance of receiving cell pickup at end of level (make a stat that adjusts this)</li></ul><h1>Bugfix</h1>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Release Notes</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>